<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Digital Strategy on MindSing</title><link>https://www.mindsing.com/tags/digital-strategy/</link><description>Recent content in Digital Strategy on MindSing</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.mindsing.com/tags/digital-strategy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why Drupal Still Matters in the Age of AI Page Builders</title><link>https://www.mindsing.com/blog/technology-innovation/why-drupal-still-matters-ai-page-builders/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.mindsing.com/blog/technology-innovation/why-drupal-still-matters-ai-page-builders/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;The enterprise CMS landscape is experiencing a familiar disruption. AI-powered page builders promise what every previous wave of &amp;ldquo;revolutionary&amp;rdquo; tools has promised: faster development, lower costs, and democratized content creation. This time, however, the capability feels genuinely different. AI can generate layouts, write copy, optimize images, and assemble functional pages in minutes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For digital leaders evaluating platform strategies, a reasonable question emerges: if AI can build pages this quickly, does a robust CMS like Drupal still matter?&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>From Brochure Site to Lead Engine</title><link>https://www.mindsing.com/blog/strategy-growth/brochure-site-to-lead-engine/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.mindsing.com/blog/strategy-growth/brochure-site-to-lead-engine/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Your website looks great. It tells your story, showcases your work, and presents your services beautifully. There&amp;rsquo;s just one problem: &lt;strong&gt;it&amp;rsquo;s not generating leads at the rate your business needs to grow&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many businesses treat their website as a digital brochure—a place to park information that might be helpful if someone already knows about you. But in reality, your website should be your hardest-working salesperson: qualifying leads 24/7, nurturing prospects automatically, and feeding your sales team a steady stream of qualified opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Rebuild vs Redesign: Digital Upgrade Guide</title><link>https://www.mindsing.com/blog/strategy-growth/rebuild-vs-redesign-digital-upgrade/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.mindsing.com/blog/strategy-growth/rebuild-vs-redesign-digital-upgrade/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;When your business is growing and your website is struggling to keep up, you face a critical decision: &lt;strong&gt;redesign&lt;/strong&gt; what you have or &lt;strong&gt;rebuild&lt;/strong&gt; from the ground up? This choice can mean the difference between a smart investment that accelerates growth and an expensive mistake that holds you back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For growth-stage businesses, this decision becomes even more crucial. You need a platform that can scale with your ambitions, support evolving marketing strategies, and integrate with your expanding tech stack—all without draining resources or disrupting operations.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>ROI of Open Source CMS Platforms</title><link>https://www.mindsing.com/blog/strategy-growth/roi-open-source-cms/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.mindsing.com/blog/strategy-growth/roi-open-source-cms/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;When evaluating a content management system, the initial license fee is just the beginning of the story. The real question decision-makers should ask isn&amp;rsquo;t &amp;ldquo;What does it cost to buy?&amp;rdquo; but rather &lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;What will it cost us to own, operate, and scale this platform over five years?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The answer might surprise you. Despite aggressive marketing from proprietary vendors positioning themselves as &amp;ldquo;enterprise-ready&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;all-in-one solutions,&amp;rdquo; the total cost of ownership (TCO) and long-term return on investment (ROI) consistently favor open source platforms—particularly Drupal and WordPress.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>