<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Design and User Experience Excellence on MindSing</title><link>https://www.mindsing.com/blog/design-experience/</link><description>Recent content in Design and User Experience Excellence on MindSing</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.mindsing.com/blog/design-experience/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Human Imperative: People Are Central to AI-Driven Design</title><link>https://www.mindsing.com/blog/design-experience/human-in-the-loop-ai-ux/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.mindsing.com/blog/design-experience/human-in-the-loop-ai-ux/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;There is a seductive promise buried in every AI design tool, every generative UI system, and every &amp;ldquo;just describe it and we&amp;rsquo;ll build it&amp;rdquo; pitch: that the hard, messy, deeply human work of designing great experiences can be automated away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It cannot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AI is a powerful accelerant. It is not a replacement for human judgment.&lt;/strong&gt; And in the domain of user experience design, that distinction is not philosophical—it has direct consequences for your users, your conversions, and your reputation.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>From Figma to Drupal: Building Design Systems that Scale</title><link>https://www.mindsing.com/blog/design-experience/figma-to-drupal-design-systems/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.mindsing.com/blog/design-experience/figma-to-drupal-design-systems/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;The handoff between design and development is where beautiful visions go to die. Designers create pixel-perfect interfaces in Figma. Developers build functional components in Drupal. And somewhere in between, consistency evaporates like morning dew.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The problem isn&amp;rsquo;t lack of talent—it&amp;rsquo;s lack of system.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A design system is the bridge between Figma and your CMS, ensuring that what designers envision is what developers build, and what gets deployed stays consistent as your site grows. But most organizations approach design systems backwards: they try to document what exists rather than establishing a shared language from the start.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Accessibility First: SEO and AI Content</title><link>https://www.mindsing.com/blog/design-experience/accessibility-seo-ai/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.mindsing.com/blog/design-experience/accessibility-seo-ai/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;When organizations think about web accessibility, they often frame it as a compliance issue or an ethical obligation. While both are true, there&amp;rsquo;s a compelling business case that&amp;rsquo;s often overlooked: &lt;strong&gt;accessibility is the foundation of effective SEO and the key to making your content discoverable by generative AI systems&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="the-convergence-of-accessibility-seo-and-ai"&gt;The Convergence of Accessibility, SEO, and AI&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Search engines and AI systems don&amp;rsquo;t browse websites the way humans do. They can&amp;rsquo;t see your beautiful design, watch your videos without captions, or interpret images without alt text. They rely on the same structured, semantic markup that makes websites accessible to people using assistive technologies.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Designing Trust in Finance &amp; Insurance UI</title><link>https://www.mindsing.com/blog/design-experience/designing-trust-finance-insurance/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.mindsing.com/blog/design-experience/designing-trust-finance-insurance/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;When someone visits an e-commerce site and doesn&amp;rsquo;t trust it, they simply don&amp;rsquo;t buy the shoes. Annoying for the retailer, but low stakes for the visitor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When someone visits a financial services or insurance website and doesn&amp;rsquo;t trust it, they&amp;rsquo;re making a decision that could impact their family&amp;rsquo;s financial future, their retirement, or their ability to recover from a disaster. &lt;strong&gt;The stakes are fundamentally different, and your UI must reflect that.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>