<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Best Practices on MindSing</title><link>https://www.mindsing.com/tags/best-practices/</link><description>Recent content in Best Practices on MindSing</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.mindsing.com/tags/best-practices/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Playwright Testing: Build Reliable End-to-End Tests</title><link>https://www.mindsing.com/blog/performance-optimization/playwright-automated-testing-guide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.mindsing.com/blog/performance-optimization/playwright-automated-testing-guide/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;End-to-end testing has a reputation problem. Tests are flaky, slow, and expensive to maintain. Teams start with enthusiasm, writing comprehensive test suites—only to watch them become brittle, unreliable, and eventually ignored.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Playwright changes this equation.&lt;/strong&gt; Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s modern testing framework addresses the core pain points that plagued previous generations of browser automation tools. With its architectural improvements, developer-friendly API, and built-in best practices, Playwright makes it possible to build automated test suites that are fast, reliable, and actually maintainable.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Getting Started with Automated Testing in Drupal</title><link>https://www.mindsing.com/blog/technology-innovation/automated-testing-drupal-getting-started/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.mindsing.com/blog/technology-innovation/automated-testing-drupal-getting-started/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Automated testing is often viewed as a &amp;ldquo;nice to have&amp;rdquo; in Drupal development—something teams plan to implement &amp;ldquo;when there&amp;rsquo;s time.&amp;rdquo; But treating testing as optional is a costly mistake. The reality is that &lt;strong&gt;automated testing is fundamental to building maintainable Drupal applications&lt;/strong&gt;, reducing bugs, and enabling teams to refactor and upgrade with confidence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This guide will walk you through the essentials of automated testing in Drupal, from basic concepts to practical implementation, helping you build a testing practice that actually fits into your development workflow.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>