<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Technology &amp; Innovation on MindSing</title><link>https://www.mindsing.com/blog/technology-innovation/</link><description>Recent content in Technology &amp; Innovation on MindSing</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.mindsing.com/blog/technology-innovation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why Drupal Still Matters in the Age of AI Page Builders</title><link>https://www.mindsing.com/blog/technology-innovation/why-drupal-still-matters-ai-page-builders/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.mindsing.com/blog/technology-innovation/why-drupal-still-matters-ai-page-builders/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;The enterprise CMS landscape is experiencing a familiar disruption. AI-powered page builders promise what every previous wave of &amp;ldquo;revolutionary&amp;rdquo; tools has promised: faster development, lower costs, and democratized content creation. This time, however, the capability feels genuinely different. AI can generate layouts, write copy, optimize images, and assemble functional pages in minutes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For digital leaders evaluating platform strategies, a reasonable question emerges: if AI can build pages this quickly, does a robust CMS like Drupal still matter?&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Native Drupal A/B Testing with Figma, Make, and MCP</title><link>https://www.mindsing.com/blog/technology-innovation/figma-make-mcp-drupal-ab-testing/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.mindsing.com/blog/technology-innovation/figma-make-mcp-drupal-ab-testing/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;A/B testing traditionally requires expensive third-party platforms, complex JavaScript integrations, or extensive custom development. But what if you could build a native, context-aware A/B testing system directly in Drupal—one that leverages your existing design system, automates variant creation, and uses AI to intelligently manage experiments?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By combining &lt;a href="https://www.mindsing.com/blog/design-experience/figma-to-drupal-design-systems/"&gt;Figma&amp;rsquo;s design variants&lt;/a&gt;, Make&amp;rsquo;s automation capabilities, and &lt;a href="https://www.mindsing.com/blog/technology-innovation/model-context-protocol-drupal/"&gt;Model Context Protocol (MCP)&lt;/a&gt; for intelligent orchestration, we can create a powerful A/B testing workflow that feels native to Drupal while remaining accessible to designers and marketers.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Model Context Protocol for Drupal</title><link>https://www.mindsing.com/blog/technology-innovation/model-context-protocol-drupal/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.mindsing.com/blog/technology-innovation/model-context-protocol-drupal/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;As &lt;a href="https://www.mindsing.com/blog/technology-innovation/ai-development-workflows/"&gt;AI tools become increasingly integrated into development workflows&lt;/a&gt;, a fundamental challenge has emerged: how do AI assistants effectively interact with complex, domain-specific systems like content management platforms? Model Context Protocol (MCP) offers an elegant solution that&amp;rsquo;s particularly relevant for Drupal developers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="what-is-model-context-protocol"&gt;What is Model Context Protocol?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Model Context Protocol (MCP) is an open protocol developed by Anthropic that standardizes how AI assistants connect to external data sources and tools. Think of it as a universal adapter that allows AI models to interact with your systems in a structured, secure, and contextually aware manner.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Tip-Toeing into the Deep: AI-Powered Development Workflows</title><link>https://www.mindsing.com/blog/technology-innovation/ai-development-workflows/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.mindsing.com/blog/technology-innovation/ai-development-workflows/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;At the 2024 Pacific Northwest Drupal Summit, MindSing sponsored a session exploring the practical integration of AI tools into modern development workflows. The session, &amp;ldquo;&lt;a href="https://pnwdrupalsummit.org/sessions/tiptoeing-deep-seek-prompt-repeat"&gt;Tip-Toeing into the Deep: Seek, Prompt, Repeat&lt;/a&gt;,&amp;rdquo; demonstrated how developers can leverage AI assistance while maintaining code quality and deepening their expertise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="video"&gt;
 &lt;div class="video__wrapper video--youtube"&gt;
 &lt;iframe 
 src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/WzG9vDnizRg" 
 title="YouTube video player" 
 frameborder="0" 
 allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" 
 referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" 
 allowfullscreen&gt;
 &lt;/iframe&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2 id="the-ai-development-revolution"&gt;The AI Development Revolution&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re in the midst of a fundamental shift in how developers work. Tools like GitHub Copilot, ChatGPT, Claude, and specialized coding assistants are no longer experimental novelties—they&amp;rsquo;re becoming integral parts of professional development workflows.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Getting Started with Automated Testing in Drupal</title><link>https://www.mindsing.com/blog/technology-innovation/automated-testing-drupal-getting-started/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.mindsing.com/blog/technology-innovation/automated-testing-drupal-getting-started/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Automated testing is often viewed as a &amp;ldquo;nice to have&amp;rdquo; in Drupal development—something teams plan to implement &amp;ldquo;when there&amp;rsquo;s time.&amp;rdquo; But treating testing as optional is a costly mistake. The reality is that &lt;strong&gt;automated testing is fundamental to building maintainable Drupal applications&lt;/strong&gt;, reducing bugs, and enabling teams to refactor and upgrade with confidence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This guide will walk you through the essentials of automated testing in Drupal, from basic concepts to practical implementation, helping you build a testing practice that actually fits into your development workflow.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Why Open Source Matters for Enterprise Web Development</title><link>https://www.mindsing.com/blog/technology-innovation/why-open-source-matters/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.mindsing.com/blog/technology-innovation/why-open-source-matters/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;In the rapidly evolving landscape of web development, choosing the right foundation for your digital infrastructure is more critical than ever. At MindSing, we&amp;rsquo;re passionate advocates for open source technologies—particularly Drupal—and here&amp;rsquo;s why.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="the-power-of-open-source"&gt;The Power of Open Source&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Open source software represents more than just freely available code. It embodies a collaborative philosophy that drives innovation, ensures transparency, and provides long-term sustainability for your digital investments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="transparency-and-security"&gt;Transparency and Security&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you build on open source platforms, you&amp;rsquo;re not locked into a proprietary black box. Every line of code is inspectable, auditable, and verifiable. This transparency is crucial for enterprise organizations and higher education institutions that must maintain strict security and compliance standards.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Why Vite Is Replacing Webpack in Modern Builds</title><link>https://www.mindsing.com/blog/technology-innovation/vite-replacing-webpack-modern-builds/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.mindsing.com/blog/technology-innovation/vite-replacing-webpack-modern-builds/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;ve been building front-end applications for the past decade, Webpack has probably been a constant companion—sometimes helpful, often frustrating, occasionally infuriating. Those 30-second (or 3-minute) build times. That sprawling configuration file that no one fully understands. The mysterious &amp;ldquo;Module not found&amp;rdquo; errors that appear only in production.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then you hear about Vite. Cold server starts in milliseconds. Hot module replacement that actually feels instant. Configuration so simple you wonder if you&amp;rsquo;re missing something.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>