<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Design Systems on MindSing</title><link>https://www.mindsing.com/tags/design-systems/</link><description>Recent content in Design Systems on MindSing</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.mindsing.com/tags/design-systems/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Native Drupal A/B Testing with Figma, Make, and MCP</title><link>https://www.mindsing.com/blog/technology-innovation/figma-make-mcp-drupal-ab-testing/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.mindsing.com/blog/technology-innovation/figma-make-mcp-drupal-ab-testing/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;A/B testing traditionally requires expensive third-party platforms, complex JavaScript integrations, or extensive custom development. But what if you could build a native, context-aware A/B testing system directly in Drupal—one that leverages your existing design system, automates variant creation, and uses AI to intelligently manage experiments?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By combining &lt;a href="https://www.mindsing.com/blog/design-experience/figma-to-drupal-design-systems/"&gt;Figma&amp;rsquo;s design variants&lt;/a&gt;, Make&amp;rsquo;s automation capabilities, and &lt;a href="https://www.mindsing.com/blog/technology-innovation/model-context-protocol-drupal/"&gt;Model Context Protocol (MCP)&lt;/a&gt; for intelligent orchestration, we can create a powerful A/B testing workflow that feels native to Drupal while remaining accessible to designers and marketers.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>From Figma to Drupal: Building Design Systems that Scale</title><link>https://www.mindsing.com/blog/design-experience/figma-to-drupal-design-systems/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.mindsing.com/blog/design-experience/figma-to-drupal-design-systems/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;The handoff between design and development is where beautiful visions go to die. Designers create pixel-perfect interfaces in Figma. Developers build functional components in Drupal. And somewhere in between, consistency evaporates like morning dew.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The problem isn&amp;rsquo;t lack of talent—it&amp;rsquo;s lack of system.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A design system is the bridge between Figma and your CMS, ensuring that what designers envision is what developers build, and what gets deployed stays consistent as your site grows. But most organizations approach design systems backwards: they try to document what exists rather than establishing a shared language from the start.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>