<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>WordPress on MindSing</title><link>https://www.mindsing.com/tags/wordpress/</link><description>Recent content in WordPress on MindSing</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.mindsing.com/tags/wordpress/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>When to Rebuild vs. Redesign: How to Plan a Smart Digital Upgrade</title><link>https://www.mindsing.com/blog/strategy-growth/rebuild-vs-redesign-digital-upgrade/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.mindsing.com/blog/strategy-growth/rebuild-vs-redesign-digital-upgrade/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;When your business is growing and your website is struggling to keep up, you face a critical decision: &lt;strong&gt;redesign&lt;/strong&gt; what you have or &lt;strong&gt;rebuild&lt;/strong&gt; from the ground up? This choice can mean the difference between a smart investment that accelerates growth and an expensive mistake that holds you back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For growth-stage businesses, this decision becomes even more crucial. You need a platform that can scale with your ambitions, support evolving marketing strategies, and integrate with your expanding tech stack—all without draining resources or disrupting operations.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>The ROI of Open Source: Why Drupal &amp; WordPress Still Beat Proprietary CMS</title><link>https://www.mindsing.com/blog/strategy-growth/roi-open-source-cms/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.mindsing.com/blog/strategy-growth/roi-open-source-cms/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;When evaluating a content management system, the initial license fee is just the beginning of the story. The real question decision-makers should ask isn&amp;rsquo;t &amp;ldquo;What does it cost to buy?&amp;rdquo; but rather &lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;What will it cost us to own, operate, and scale this platform over five years?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The answer might surprise you. Despite aggressive marketing from proprietary vendors positioning themselves as &amp;ldquo;enterprise-ready&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;all-in-one solutions,&amp;rdquo; the total cost of ownership (TCO) and long-term return on investment (ROI) consistently favor open source platforms—particularly Drupal and WordPress.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>